Guide to the Photographs by and relating to Allen Ginsberg MSS.PHOTO.0450
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Contact Sheets, Series 2
  - Contact sheet 89, 1962 Dec. 25; 89 (Item 3)
    "Taj Mahal, India; 6-12 Taj Mahal views; Peter & friends, Ronnie Vail, "Ershenberg"; 13-34 smoking ganja in cupola at Fathepur Sikri; Tansen's cupola? a stage where the singer Tansen entertained the Moslem top men?; Xmas 1962, Agra Taj Mahal and Fthepur Sikri crowd over Xmas"
  - Contact sheet 90, 1962 Oct. 20; 90 (Item 3)
    "N. Calcutta, India; Kali Puja (worship ;holiday) w/Asok Fakir row 1; row 3 Asok Fahir and Saddhu smoking chiliam on Howrah Bridge; side drummers on Kali parade"
  - Contact sheet 100, 1963 July 1; 100 (Item 4)
    "Vancouver, Canada; Seattle, WA; #1815 Phil Whalen, Seattle, Jerry Hesierman; poetry conference; #1822 Whalen, Hassan, Indian, Tom Jackrell en route Vancouver; #1820 "gas stop near Portland, returning from Van couv er poetry conference, Tom Jackrell (author of epic poem on Campbell's tomato soup); Whalen, Ginsberg""
  - Contact sheet 101, 1964 Jan. 1; 101 (Item 4)
    "Millbrook, NY; Ken Kesey's bus 'Further'"
  - Contact sheet 102, 1964 Jan. 1; 102 (Item 4)
    Neal Cassady
  - Contact sheet 103, 1964 Jan. 1; 103 (Item 4)
    New York City; Jack Kerouac final pictures
  - Contact sheet 104, 1964 Jan. 1; 104 (Item 4)
    New York City; Peter Orlovsky on the roof
  - Contact sheet 105, 1964 Jan. 1; 105 (Item 4)
    "Cherry Valley, NY?; NYC, Moscow, Russia; #2008 Vosnesensky alone coming on street to stairway of Bristol Hotel?, Moscow; #2006-07 Aksionov, prose, Yevtuchenko, AG & Rosdevtsensky, poet, Moscow"
  - Contact sheet 106, 1965 Mar. 1; 106 (Item 4)
    "Leningrad, Moscow, Russia; Andrei Vosnesensky approaching hotel, Rosdevnetsky, Yevtuchenko, Red Square, Mayakovsky's grave, Moscow Writers Union [March 1965]; Red Square; AG at Kremlin Wall with Lenin's tomb behind, line at Lenin's tomb, cobblestones of square; #2043 St. Petersburg, Leningrad; Vosnesensky's Theater of Poetry; Aksionov, Yevtuchenko and wives"
  - Contact sheet 107, 1965 Mar. 1; 107 (Item 4)
    "Leningrad, Moscow, Russia [March 1965]; Prague, Czechoslovakia; March-May 1965 [Prague, May 1, 1965]; King of May parade, Moscow Writers Union, Alexei Ginzberg ca. April 8, 1965; #2067 Yessinin-Volpine April 8?, 1965; #2073 AG & Sergei Yessenin-Volpine vodka toast to poesy, Moscow, in his apartment; #2075 Alexei Ginzberg & AG photo by S. yessenin-Volpine in his Moscow apartment (both presently in jail or madhouse 1970?); #2091 oath to suvert the State thru poesy; #2075 MMe Volpine; S. Yesseinin Volpine, mathematician poet and son of Yessenin, AG, Alexei Ginzburg, underground poet and editor; #2100 Alexei and wife; #2118-2122 Yevgeny Yevtushenko; #2123 Bulova, guitar folk singer; #2125 Yevtuchenko's nervous wringled (sp?) eyes, in restaurant; #2084 "Float to park in front of Hotel Park of Culture, May King and Polytechnic students, May Day 1965, Prague; #2115 "during or after Pargue May Day parade, with economic/philospher and friends cafe, Zdena Squaretyka; #2086 Red Square, waiting for Cosmonauts, anniversary of revolution crowd?; #2117 Polytechnic students Hotel Merkur Prague Kral Majales preparation May 1, 1965; #2116 Polytechnic students Prague Kral Majales preparations, requested to become May King candidate at hotel; #2112 May Day parade morning with Marxist Existentialist economist Ivan Svitak"
  - Contact sheet 108.1, 1965 Aug. 1; 108.1 (Item 4)
    "London, Glacier Park, Berkeley, San Francisco; Berkeley Downey Street Poetry Conference; London Albert Hall; Peace Eye"
    London Albert Hall
  - Contact sheet 108.2, 1966 Aug. 1; 108.2 (Item 4)
    "London, Glacier Park, Berkeley, San Francisco; Frank O'Hara's cocktail funeral? Eugene Brooks and sons beside open casket (is this Louis Ginsberg funeral?)"
  - Contact sheet 109.1, 1967 Aug. 1; 109.1 (Item 4)
    "Venice, Italy"
  - Contact sheet 109.2, 1967 Aug. 1; 109.2 (Item 4)
    "COLOR: Venice, Pisa, Italy; (date?) "
  - Contact sheet 110, 1967 Nov. 1; 110 (Item 4)
    "Venice, Genoa, Italy; San Gregorio, The Squero (boat yard), Pound's House, Nanda Pivano, Ettore Sottsass, their house near Genoa; #2277 Gerald Malanga"
  - Contact sheet 111, 1967 Aug. 1; 111 (Item 4)
    "Venice, Italy; San Marco"
  - Contact sheet 112, 1967 Aug. 1; 112 (Item 4)
    "Paris, France; Luxembourg Gardens, Louvre"
  - Contact sheet 113, 1967 Aug. 1; 113 (Item 4)
    "Paris, France; Venice, Italy"
  - Contact sheet 114, 1967 Aug. 1; 114 (Item 4)
    "Paris, France; Venice, Italy; Louvre, Mona Lisa, Eiffel Tower, Bridge of Sighs, San Marco"
  - Contact sheet 115, 1967 Aug. 1; 115 (Item 4)
    "COLOR: Venice, Italy"
  - Contact sheet 116, 1968 Jan. 1; 116 (Item 4)
    "San Francisco, in car"
  - Contact sheet 117, 1968 Jan. 1; 117 (Item 4)
  - Contact sheet 118, 1968 Jan. 1; 118 (Item 4)
  - Contact sheet 119, 1968 Jan. 1; 119 (Item 4)
  - Contact sheet 120, 1968 Jan. 1; 120 (Item 4)
    "San Francisco, CA; Allen Ginsberg picketing hotel; City Lights with Philip Whalen"
  - Contact sheet 91, 1962 Oct. 20; 91 (Item 4)
    "N. Calcutta, India; Kail Puja, Kali Ma; row 1: Peter & beggar Baul Lady Calcutta; row 2 Kiosk, beggar starving fainted malnutrition, Peter passing observing shadow play, Kali curtain; beggar cripple; row 3: Calcutta College coffeehouse poets at home, L. Sunil Ganguley, center maybe Tarapada Roy or Shakti Chatterji; #1487 "collapsed near Government Buildings, Chowinghee, Calcutta; #1476 "blind beggar lady on street to Chinatown from Hotel Amjadia; #1478 "man collapsed on Chowringtree""
  - Contact sheet 92.1, 1962 Oct 20; 92.1 (Item 4)
    "N. Calcutta, India; Kail Puja, Kali Ma, religious procession, Howrah Bridge"
  - Contact sheet 92.2, 1962 Oct 20; 92.2 (Item 4)
    "N. Calcutta, India; Peter Orlovsky with shaved head; musicians"
  - Contact sheet 93, 1963 July 1; 93 (Item 4)
    Japan; Buddhist shrines
  - Contact sheet 94, 1963 July 1; 94 (Item 4)
    "Kyoto, Japan; Buddhist shrines, #10-11 Cid Corman; Roy Kyuka; Kyoto from (Kogoson?) mountain"
  - Contact sheet 95, 1963 July 1; 95 (Item 4)
    Japan; Sea of Japan
  - Contact sheet 96, 1963 Jan. 1; 96 (Item 4)
    "Paterson, NJ; NYC; Bob Thompson opening"
  - Contact sheet 97, 1963 July 1; 97 (Item 4)
    "Vancouver, Canada; poetry conference; #1711 AG, Margaret Avison, Robert Duncan; #1731 Creeley, Bobbie Creeley, AG; #1733 David Schaff, Yalie?, Duncan, Creeley, Hawkins, Don Allen, Olson"
  - Contact sheet 98, 1963 July 1; 98 (Item 4)
    "Vancouver, Canada; poetry conference"
  - Contact sheet 99, 1963 July 1; 99 (Item 4)
  - Contact sheet 122, 1968 Jan. 1; 122 (Item 5)
    "Cherry Valley, NY (1967-69?); Peter Orlovsky, clothed and naked in snow at farm"
  - Contact sheet 123.1, 1968 Jan. 1; 123.1 (Item 5)
    "St. Petersburg, FL; Cherry Valley, NY (1967-69?); E. 10th St.?, NYC; Park Ave. & Vreeland Ave. near Burger's Newspaper Store/Luncheonette, Paterson, NJ; Stella Kerouac? at house in Florida, 1971? 72?, Peter Orlovsky, Julius Orlovsky, Denise Mercedes, Allen Ginsberg, Louis Ginsberg, (after attack?)"
  - Contact sheet 123.2, 1968 Jan. 1; 123.2 (Item 5)
    "Cherry Valley, NY; NYC; 5A-6A Al Aronowitz, Ed Urich, Bessie Smith (the Jersey cow), Gordon Ball, #20 & 15A Enrique Benvenutti"
  - Contact sheet 123.3, 1968 Jan. 1; 123.3 (Item 5)
    "Tucson, AZ; Oregon; Cherry Valley; Drummond Hadley scribbling in Tucson"
  - Contact sheet 124, 1971 Jan. 1; 124 (Item 5)
    "Benares, India; Kabir-Mata double-exposure"
  - Contact sheet 125, 1971 Jan. 1; 125 (Item 5)
    "India; street scenes, ancient ruins"
  - Contact sheet 126, 1971 Jan. 1; 126 (Item 5)
    COLOR: India?
  - Contact sheet 127, 1971 Jan. 1; 127 (Item 5)
    "Kitkitdizzie, CA?; Australia or Fiji?"
  - Contact sheet 128, 1971 Jan. 1; 128 (Item 5)
    COLOR: Puerto Rico
    Lucien Carr
  - Contact sheet 129, 1971 Jan. 1; 129 (Item 5)
    "Puerto Rico; tow truck, fishing"
  - Contact sheet 130, 1971 Jan. 1; 130 (Item 5)
    Puerto Rico; Paterson?
  - Contact sheet 131, 1972 Mar. 1; 131 (Item 5)
    "Australia, Fiji?"
  - Contact sheet 132, 1972 Mar. 23; 132 (Item 5)
    "Adelaide?, Brisbane?, Australia; (High on mushrooms at Ayer's Rock), week of March 23; Athabascan Village Alaska - April 1972; Andrei Vosnosensky in hotel tower?,dog sleds"
  - Contact sheet 133.1, 1972 Jan. 1; 133.1 (Item 5)
    "Santa Fe, NM; Larry Lillebird (or Littlebird?), at David Padwa's house; Tsultrim Trip, 1972?"
  - Contact sheet 133.2, 1972 Jan. 1; 133.2 (Item 5)
    "COLOR: Santa Fe, NM; Paterson, NJ; at David Padwa's house"
  - Contact sheet 134, 1972 Jan. 1; 134 (Item 5)
    "Tetons, Denver; Tsultrim Allione in nun garb"
  - Contact sheet 135, 1972 Jan. 1; 135 (Item 5)
    "Tetons, Denver; Montana; Allen Ginsberg; Justin Brierley; Ed White; Bob Burford - Denver; Ron Zimardi, Tsultrim Allione - Montana"
  - Contact sheet 136, 1973 Jan. 1; 136 (Item 5)
    "Iona Island, broke leg?"
  - Contact sheet 137, 1973 Jan. 1; 137 (Item 5)
    Scotland
  - Contact sheet 138.1, 1973 Jan. 1; 138.1 (Item 5)
    "Newcastle, London; grave of Charles Osborne Provis Gibson, Durham Cathedral, Bede's grave, to a Northumbrian Church Yard, Christopher Logue, Portobello Rd."
  - Contact sheet 138.2, 1973 Jan. 1; 138.2 (Item 5)
    Northumbria
  - Contact sheet 139.1, 1973 Jan. 1; 139.1 (Item 5)
    "Portobello; Vondel Park Poetry Festival, Allen Ginsberg on crutches"
  - Contact sheet 139.2, 1973 Jan. 1; 139.2 (Item 5)
    "Paris, France [1973?] "
  - Contact sheet 139.3, 1973 Jan. 1; 139.3 (Item 5)
  - Contact sheet 140.1, 1974 Jan. 1; 140.1 (Item 5)
    "NYC; Paterson, NJ; William Burroughs and artist in Franklyn Street loft, 1974-75?"
  - Contact sheet 140.2, 1977 Oct. 1; 140.2 (Item 5)
    "Munich, Germany; Bierstube group"
  - Contact sheet 140.3, 1978 Oct. 1; 140.3 (Item 5)
    "Boulder, CO; New Mexico; Tupelo, MS; 1978?: 0-5 Kate Millett, Varsity Apts. Marine & Broadway; 8-9 AG, Steven Schoen, Robert Creeley, Larry Fagin, Peter Orlovsky, the late Alan Marlowe, tall figure in back?, his then boyfriend co-worker in landscape business; 10-11 Lee Hill friend of W.S.B.; 19-35 Georgia O'Keefe at her house in New Mexico with her secretary, my student and Peter Orlovsky on O'Keefe's roof; Gordon Ball"
  - Contact sheet 140.4, 1976 July 1; 140.4 (Item 5)
    "Salt Lake City, UT"
  - Contact sheet 141.1, 1973 July 1; 141.1 (Item 5)
    "Scotland; Corn Close, Lake District, Manchester?, Birmingham?, England; Jonathon Williams in Yorkshire Dales, Grasmere, Scott Eden at Buddhist Center (Karme Thinley), Wordsworth's grave, Lama Veseley, 1975?"
  - Contact sheet 141.2, 1973 July 1; 141.2 (Item 5)
    "COLOR: Sante Fe, NM"
  - Contact sheet 141.3, 1975 July 1; 141.3 (Item 5)
  - Contact sheet 141.4, 1975 July 1; 141.4 (Item 5)
    "Park Ave., Paterson, Morristown, Glassboro, NJ; Louis Ginsberg at home in armchair, trip to Morristown/Glassboro visit to Whitman's house, first meet with Steven Taylor?"
  - Contact sheet 141.5, 1979 May 1; 141.5 (Item 5)
  - Contact sheet 141.6, 1978 Sept. 1; 141.6 (Item 5)
    "Bedrock Mortar, CA"
  - Contact sheet 141.7, 1978 Jan. 1; 141.7 (Item 5)
    "Cherry Valley, NY; NYC"
  - Contact sheet 141.9, 1979 Sept. 1; 141.9 (Item 5)
    "COLOR: Milan, Rome, Italy; Living Theater"
  - Contact sheet 142.1, 1979 Sept. 1; 142.1 (Item 5)
  - Contact sheet 142.2, 1979 June 1; 142.2 (Item 5)
    England
  - Contact sheet 142.3, 1979 Oct. 1; 142.3 (Item 5)
    "Kitkitdizee, San Francisco, CA"
  - Contact sheet 142.4, 1979 Oct. 1; 142.4 (Item 5)
    "Kitkitdizee, CA"
  - Contact sheet 142.5, 1979 Oct. 1; 142.5 (Item 5)
    "COLOR: Kitkitdizze, CA"
  - Contact sheet 142.6, 1979 Nov. 1; 142.6 (Item 5)
    "COLOR: London, Oxford, England; The Rosetta Stone"
  - Contact sheet 142.7A, 1979 Nov. 1; 142.7 (Item 5)
    "Brighton, England; Blake's Cottage; Public House Bookshop"
  - Contact sheet 142.7B, 1979 Nov. 1; 142.7 (Item 5)
    "England; Paris, France"
  - Contact sheet 142.8, 1979 Nov. 1; 142.8 (Item 5)
    "Brighton, Felphan, England; Blake's Cottage; Public House Bookshop"
  - Contact sheet 142.9, 1979 Dec. 1; 142.9 (Item 5)
    "Tubingen, Germany"
  - Contact sheet 143.1, 1980 Jan. 1; 143.1 (Item 6)
    "COLOR: Boulder, CO"
  - Contact sheet 143.2, 1980 Feb. 23; 143.2 (Item 6)
    "Boulder, CO; 1439 Mapleton, Allen Ginsberg and Peter Orlovsky working on proofs of Straight Heart's Delight"
  - Contact sheet 143.3, 1980 Mar. 1; 143.3 (Item 6)
  - Contact sheet 143.4, 1980 Apr. 30; 143.4 (Item 6)
    "Boulder, CO; Naropa"
    University of Colorado
  - Contact sheet 143.5, 1980 May 1; 143.5 (Item 6)
    "Banff, Canada; airplane views of Mt. Saint Helens' volcano; Lake Victoria seminary, Buffalo Art Park"
  - Contact sheet 143.6, 1980 June 1; 143.6 (Item 6)
    "Boulder, CO; Santa Fe, NM; Buffalo, NY; car trip Boulder to Santa Fe"
  - Contact sheet 143.7, 1980 Sept. 1; 143.7 (Item 6)
    "Cherry Valley, NY; Kansas City"
  - Contact sheet 143.8, 1980 Sept. 1; 143.8 (Item 6)
    "Europe, on train, Fall 1980"
  - Contact sheet 143.9, 1980 Sept. 1; 143.9 (Item 6)
    "Europe, Yugoslavia; Budapest, Fall 1980; Poets Conference visit to Yugoslavia on way to Novi Pasar; Sopocani Church; PO and old phone Budapest"
  - Contact sheet 144.1, 1980 Sept. 1; 144.1 (Item 6)
    "Heidelberg, Germany; Zurich, Switzerland; James Joyce's grave in Zurich"
  - Contact sheet 144.2, 1980 Sept. 1; 144.2 (Item 6)
  - Contact sheet 144.3, 1980 Sept. 1; 144.3 (Item 6)
    "Vienna, Austria; Germany; Ludwig's Castle (Neuschwanstein), Vienna with Dharmadata Folk"
  - Contact sheet 144.4, 1981 Jan. 1; 144.4 (Item 6)
  - Contact sheet 144.5A, 1981 Aug. 1; 144.5 (Item 6)
    "Morelos, Mexico"
  - Contact sheet 144.5B, 1981 Sept. 1; 144.5 (Item 6)
    "COLOR: New York City; Naples, Italy; Long Island"
  - Contact sheet 144.6, 1982 Jan. 1; 144.6 (Item 6)
    Nicaragua; Sandinistas
  - Contact sheet 144.7, 1982 Jan. 1; 144.7 (Item 6)
    Nicaragua; Dodie Muller smoking cigarette at her New Years Eve party
  - Contact sheet 144.8A, 1982 Jan. 1; 144.8 (Item 6)
    Nicaragua
  - Contact sheet 144.8B, 1982 Jan. 1; 144.8 (Item 6)
    Nicaragua; village scenes
  - Contact sheet 144.9, 1982 Jan. 1; 144.9 (Item 6)
  - Contact sheet 145.1, 1982 Aug. 1; 145.1 (Item 6)
    COLOR: Mexico
  - Contact sheet 145.2, 1982 Aug. 1; 145.2 (Item 6)
    Mexico
  - Contact sheet 145.3, 1982 Aug. 1; 145.3 (Item 6)
  - Contact sheet 145.4, 1982 Aug. 1; 145.4 (Item 6)
  - Contact sheet 145.5, 1982 Aug. 1; 145.5 (Item 6)
  - Contact sheet 145.6, 1982 Aug. 1; 145.6 (Item 6)
  - Contact sheet 145.7, 1982 Aug. 1; 145.7 (Item 6)
    COLOR: Mexico; Allen Ginsberg self portrait
  - Contact sheet 145.8, 1982 Sept. 1; 145.8 (Item 6)
    New York City; The Clash
  - Contact sheet 145.9, 1982 Sept. 1; 145.9 (Item 6)
    New York City; The Clash concert
  - Contact sheet 146.1, 1982 Sept. 1; 146.1 (Item 7)
    New York City; [Sept. 1982?]
  - Contact sheet 146.2, 1982 Sept. 1; 146.2 (Item 7)
    New York City; street scenes; post office lines; Mary Help of Christians Church windows
  - Contact sheet 147, 1982 Sept. 1; 147 (Item 7)
    COLOR: New York City; (mid-Sept.)
  - Contact sheet 148, 1982 Sept. 1; 148 (Item 7)
    COLOR: New York City; (late Sept.); Gem Spa; St. Marks Church
  - Contact sheet 149, 1982 Sept. 1; 149 (Item 7)
    New York City; Chinese delegation in Los Angeles
  - Contact sheet 150, 1982 Oct. 1; 150 (Item 7)
    "Boulder, CO"
  - Contact sheet 151, 1982 Dec. 1; 151 (Item 7)
    "Paris, France; Los Angeles; UNESCO backstage"
    UNESCO
  - Contact sheet 152, 1982 Dec. 1; 152 (Item 7)
    "Paris, France"
  - Contact sheet 153, 1982 Dec. 1; 153 (Item 7)
    "Toulouse, France; Paris; Milan, Italy; Paris War on War, Lawrence Ferlinghetti reads; Steven Taylor accompanies Shiraishu in Milan"
  - Contact sheet 154, 1982 Dec. 1; 154 (Item 7)
    "Amsterdam, Chateville; Rimbaud Festival in Chateville"
  - Contact sheet 155, 1982 Dec. 1; 155 (Item 7)
    COLOR: Amsterdam; (Dec. 1982-Jan. 1983); Combat Rock
  - Contact sheet 156, 1983 Jan. 2; 156 (Item 7)
    COLOR: Amsterdam; Sept. on Jessore Road
  - Contact sheet 157, 1983 Jan. 1; 157 (Item 7)
    Amsterdam
  - Contact sheet 158, Jan. 1 1983; 158 (Item 7)
    Amsterdam; Antwerp; Reading at Melkweg - Amsterdam
  - Contact sheet 159, Jan. 1 1983; 159 (Item 7)
    "Oslo, Norway; Stockholm, Sweden; on boat (Jan.-Feb.)"
  - Contact sheet 160, Jan. 1 1983; 160 (Item 7)
    Berlin; subway to East Berlin; at Academe der Kurek; (Jan.-Feb.)
    Academe der Kurek
  - Contact sheet 161, Jan. 1 1983; 161 (Item 7)
    Aarhus; Upsala; Viking mounds near Upsala
  - Contact sheet 162, 1983 Feb. 1; 162 (Item 7)
    "Paterson, NJ"
  - Contact sheet 163, 1983 Mar. 1; 163 (Item 7)
    "New York City; Boulder, CO; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Naropa summer 1983"
    Rocky Mountain Dharma Center
  - Contact sheet 164.1, 1983 Aug. 1; 164.1 (Item 7)
  - Contact sheet 164.2, 1983 Aug. 1; 164.2 (Item 7)
  - Contact sheet 165.1, 1983 Aug. 1; 165.1 (Item 7)
    "Orono, ME; William Carlos Williams Conference at Orono"
  - Contact sheet 165.2, 1983 Aug. 1; 165.2 (Item 7)
  - Contact sheet 166, 1983 Aug. 1; 166 (Item 7)
    "Orono, ME; New York City; William Carlos Williams Conference at Orono; Mary Help of Christians Church window; Carl Solomon fishing"
  - Contact sheet 167, 1983 Aug. 1; 167 (Item 7)
    New York City; Carl Solomon fishing
  - Contact sheet 168, 1983 Sept. 1; 168 (Item 7)
    New York City; police scene outside window
  - Contact sheet 169, 1983 Sept. 1; 169 (Item 7)
    "COLOR: Rocky Flats, Boulder, CO"
  - Contact sheet 170.1, 1983 Nov. 1; 170.1 (Item 7)
    New York City; Colorado; Allen Ginsberg in Southern Colorado; truck outside window
  - Contact sheet 170.2, 1984 Mar. 7; 170.2 (Item 7)
    New York City; garbage truck
  - Contact sheet 171, 1984 Jan. 1; 171 (Item 7)
    New York City; at Frank's studio 7 Bleecker St.
  - Contact sheet 172, 1984 Feb. 1; 172 (Item 7)
    COLOR: New York City; William Burroughs book signing; dinner at Limelight nightclub
  - Contact sheet 173, 1984 Feb. 1; 173 (Item 7)
    "New York City; William Burroughs' 70th Birthday Party, Limelight, NYC"
  - Contact sheet 174, 1984 Feb. 1; 174 (Item 7)
    "New York City, Seattle; William Burroughs' Book Signing; dinner at Victor Bockris' house; Bob LaVigne in Seattle"
  - Contact sheet 175, 1984 Feb. 1; 175 (Item 7)
    New York City; Kenward Elmslie at St. Mark's; on Brooklyn Bridge
  - Contact sheet 176, 1984 Feb. 1; 176 (Item 8)
    "New York City, Brooklyn; on Brooklyn Bridge"
  - Contact sheet 177, 1984 Feb. 1; 177 (Item 8)
    New York City; Reed Bye on way to seminary
  - Contact sheet 178, 1984 Feb. 1; 178 (Item 8)
    "New York City; John Giorno at Bunker, subway"
  - Contact sheet 179, 1984 Mar. 1; 179 (Item 8)
    "Washington, DC; New York City"
    Washington DC UPI office
  - Contact sheet 180, 1984 Mar. 1; 180 (Item 8)
    New York City; Robert Frank's pad
  - Contact sheet 181, 1984 Mar. 1; 181 (Item 8)
    "New York City; Marisol Escobar's opening, Janis Gallery"
  - Contact sheet 182, 1984 Mar. 1; 182 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 183, 1984 Mar. 1; 183 (Item 8)
    New York City; street scenes
  - Contact sheet 184, 1984 Apr. 1; 184 (Item 8)
    London; New York City; Albert Hall reading
  - Contact sheet 185, 1984 Apr. 1; 185 (Item 8)
    London; Albert Hall reading; Tom Maschler at Jonathan Cape publishers
  - Contact sheet 186, 1984 Apr. 1; 186 (Item 8)
    Philadelphia
  - Contact sheet 187, 1984 Apr. 1; 187 (Item 8)
    "Philadelphia, PA; Atlanta, GA; Martin Luther King Memorial; (April-May)"
  - Contact sheet 188, 1984 May 1; 188 (Item 8)
    "Atlanta, GA; New York City; Martin Luther King Memorial"
  - Contact sheet 189, 1984 May 1; 189 (Item 8)
    New York City; Belgium
  - Contact sheet 190, 1984 May 1; 190 (Item 8)
    "Brussels, Belgium; IV Nacht Poetry Reading"
  - Contact sheet 191, 1984 May 1; 191 (Item 8)
    "Brussels, Belgium; railroad"
    Hotel Metropole
  - Contact sheet 192, 1984 May 1; 192 (Item 8)
    "Brussels, Belgium; street scenes, cathedral"
  - Contact sheet 193, 1984 May 1; 193 (Item 8)
    New York City; Union Square
  - Contact sheet 194, 1984 June 1; 194 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 195, 1984 June 1; 195 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 196, 1984 June 1; 196 (Item 8)
    New York City; Family Reunion; Obsure Genius photos with Antler
  - Contact sheet 197, 1984 June 1; 197 (Item 8)
    "New Smyrna, Florida"
    Atlantic Center for the Arts
  - Contact sheet 198, 1984 June 1; 198 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 199, 1984 June 1; 199 (Item 8)
    "New Smyrna, Florida; (taken with Robert Frank's polaroid)"
  - Contact sheet 200, 1984 June 1; 200 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 201, 1984 June 1; 201 (Item 8)
    "New York City; New Smyrna, FL; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 202, 1984 June 1; 202 (Item 8)
    "New York City; at Ritz Benefit, Julian Beck in hospital"
  - Contact sheet 203, 1984 June 1; 203 (Item 8)
    New York City; Tompkins Square Arts Festival; fat lady
  - Contact sheet 204, 1984 July 1; 204 (Item 8)
    "Boulder, CO; at Naropa"
  - Contact sheet 205, 1984 July 1; 205 (Item 8)
    "Boulder, CO; at Naropa; family reunion"
  - Contact sheet 206, 1984 July 1; 206 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 207, 1984 July 1; 207 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 208, 1984 July 1; 208 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 209, 1984 August 1; 209 (Item 8)
    "New York City; Woodstock (Aug. 17, 1984); Joel Gaidemack wedding with Melinda and Joel and Preacher and crowd at Delhi, NY (Aug. 19, 1984); Mrs. Meyers portrait #24-26, 23rd St. scene anonymous"
  - Contact sheet 210, 1984 August 1; 210 (Item 8)
    "New York City; kitchen window (437 E. 12th St.); Al Aronowitz (Aug. 18, 1984); Karp and Ed Sanders at Omega Institute"
    Omega Institute
  - Contact sheet 211, 1984 August 1; 211 (Item 8)
    "COLOR: New York City, subway shots"
  - Contact sheet 212, 1984 August 1; 212 (Item 8)
    "New York City, Aug. - Sept.; Rosebud and Simon Pettet's wedding"
  - Contact sheet 213, 1984 August 1; 213 (Item 8)
    "Jones Beach, NY, Aug. - Sept.; Allen Ginsberg at beach; Time photographer"
    Time
  - Contact sheet 214, 1984 Sept. 1; 214 (Item 8)
    New York City; NJ; Jonathan Robbins at Kiev restaurant; Abe Ginsberg in bed at nursing home
  - Contact sheet 215, 1984 Sept. 1; 215 (Item 8)
    New York City; Istvan Eorsi in my office; Hospital scene from "Father Death Blues" at Ellis Island Museum
    Ellis Island Museum
  - Contact sheet 216, 1984 Sept. 1; 216 (Item 8)
    "New York City; Barnet, VT; at Karma Choling"
  - Contact sheet 217, 1984 Sept. 1; 217 (Item 8)
    New York City; Labor Day weekend at Karma Choling
  - Contact sheet 218, 1984 Sept. 1; 218 (Item 8)
    New York City; at Public Theater
    Public Theater
  - Contact sheet 219, 1984 Sept. 1; 219 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 220, 1984 Sept. 1; 220 (Item 8)
    New York City; Anne Waldman being made up at Public Theater
  - Contact sheet 221, 1984 Oct. 1; 221 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 222, 1984 Oct. 1; 222 (Item 8)
    New York City; 118 Hudon St. at Osvalod Gomariz House (Sept. 5) reading; subway shots
  - Contact sheet 223, 1984 Oct. 1; 223 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 224, 1984 Oct. 1; 224 (Item 8)
    "New York City; street people on the Lower East Side; homeless; political poster; Lady on 2nd Ave. between 8th & 9th St., between library; 2nd Avenue Deli"
  - Contact sheet 225, 1984 Oct. 1; 225 (Item 8)
    "New York City; Washington, DC"
  - Contact sheet 226, 1984 Oct. 1; 226 (Item 8)
    New York City; street scenes; Chinese people and wedding on the Brooklyn Bridge
  - Contact sheet 227, 1984 Oct. 1; 227 (Item 8)
  - Contact sheet 228, 1984 Oct. 1; 228 (Item 8)
    "New York City; Paterson, NJ; Edith Ginsberg in her kitchen and family cemetery plot"
  - Contact sheet 229, 1984 Oct. 1; 229 (Item 8)
    "New York City; Los Angeles, CA"